Hey everybody, we are joined by the
Packers director of player personnel,
John Wojciechowski. Woj, thank you for
being with us.
Tell me about Dean Lowry Dennis Sutton.
Yeah, Dean Lowry Dennis Sutton, he's he
is a pass rusher.
He's got size.
Uh
he can chase down the quarterback and
chase down running backs. We're very
excited that he was available then. I
mean, he's got some crazy measurables.
[music]
He's almost 6 6, weighs 255 260. And he
ran a 4 6 3. You got some tools there,
guy, huh? Absolutely.
>> Is that what you call traits in the biz?
It's called traits and it's called
traits that had production in college,
though. Tell me what kind of a young man
he is. Is football important to him?
Attitude stuff, you know what I mean?
Yeah, no, absolutely. You can see it you
can see it in his play. Um
you know, he he he'll be relentless. He
is still green, if you'll let me say
that. You know, I know he's had
production, but we're very excited.
Where do you see him fitting in right
away? Pass rusher, every down guy, how
do you look at that?
>> I think initially with with a lot of,
you know, the young guys come in at that
position, I think yeah, you kind of look
at the pass rush and the possibilities
with him, you know, working in there.
It's a good room to be in, so. Didn't
Micah Parsons, that fellow named Micah,
didn't he go to Penn State, too? He sure
[snorts] did. Yes, exactly.
>> Well, hopefully you struck gold twice.
Real quick, Brandon Smith. Yes. The
first player you guys picked in this
draft. What do you think? Uh
competitive, goes after the ball.
He he's tough. He he has a passion for
this game. Yeah, he'll he'll be he'll be
a fun one for everyone to watch. How
about big Chris McLellan? Yeah, big
Chris, another big guy inside that has
the size and the strength to hold down
in there against the run. What's really
intriguing for his size, I mean, he
really has the potential to to work on
his pass rush and help us out on that
aspect, also.
Woj, thanks for being with us. Good luck
the rest of the way. And folks, this guy
is something else. Doesn't he look good?
Lost 39 lbs. Way to go, Woj.